(Kim Kang Min plays Choi Si Yeol)
(Park Jin Woo plays Na Aijun)
(Byung Hun as Yeon Joo Ha)
(Kim Hongjun plays Ji Kyusung)
("My idol is chasing me?!")
Because today is the first day
So I failed many times
It seems to have caused a lot of trouble to everyone.
sorry
You don't need to apologize
This is also my first time filming a variety show
I'm also nervous inside
Are professional artists like you nervous?
It's amazing
Isn’t this the first time I’m shooting today?
If we finish today successfully
Do you want to...
Help fulfill the other person’s wish
Wish?
Don't you want me to do something for you?
My words...
have a wish
You will…
Help me fulfill my wish
We'll see each other often in the next few weeks
Let’s get acquainted with it more.
Shi Lie, how much longer do you need?
I'm ready
If you think about your wish, tell me again. There is no rush.
Then can I ask you to take a photo for me?
I want to show off to my friends that I filmed with you
Things like photos
Take as many pictures as you want
So let's go find trainee teachers.
CUT OK
Teacher Luo Aijun, your expression is indeed much better.
thank you
Teacher Aijun, let’s confirm the video first
(thank you)
(Episode 3 How dare I ignore the message from my life!?)
This is really too much, right?
(Contact person Choi Si Yeol)
No, seeing me in person is enough.
I actually got his contact number
(Contact person Choi Si Yeol)
I really want to call him, I really want to hear his voice
Si Yeol’s voice heard through the phone
I really want to listen to it once and see it
No, Luo Aijun, please figure out the situation.
Why are you calling him? Are you saying you are his crush?
But this once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
Right in front of you
(Hiding his identity as a fan and continuing to work in school)
(Uncover the identity of a fan and become a successful fan)
Shi Yeol that I long for so much
right in front of my eyes
(Hiding his identity as a fan and continuing to work in school)
(Uncover the identity of a fan and become a successful fan)
The day for acting teacher renewal is coming soon
If the identity of my fanboy is revealed...
The school interview can be repeated
But Shi Lie...
(Uncover the identity of a fan and become a successful fan)
If Shi Yeol leaves, he will never come back.
(Hiding his identity as a fan and continuing to work in school)
(Uncover the identity of a fan and become a successful fan)
But you don’t have to think about it to know that Shi Yeol will feel very uncomfortable.
Because he thought I was just a muggle
(Note: For those who are not chasing stars)
Wrong
I already got his phone number. Is it necessary to think so much?
(Uncover the identity of a fan and become a successful fan)
But...
I'm still afraid of going back to the life of a homeless person
Because students are reading other books in class
So I scolded them a little bit.
Teacher Luo Aijun
What do you think of our school?
Why hire a teacher with no education or experience?
What do you mean...
The abilities are almost the same so that they don’t look out of place.
Anyway, don't be too aggressive.
As long as you stay safe as you are now
Just take care of this empty seat.
Got it?
OK I got it
No matter what
It's better to maintain the status quo, right?
It's just a breath of spring breeze...
Like the fleeting Yang Yan...
That’s it…
Really, what are you talking about in your room?
I thought you were doing Peleg
I ordered fried chicken delivery
Come out and help eat
Fried chicken?
When you broke up with me
Do you have an acceptable reason for me?
if i say
I don't want you to hinder your future because of me
You have…
New target, right?
I know you will definitely want to save me
Yeah
What's wrong
Why do you order midnight snacks?
No reason, I just feel a little empty in my stomach
What about you?
Leave your account number and it will sell badly over there.
Not living well now
do you know what this is
what is this
Si Yeol’s phone number
I exchanged contact information with Si Yeol today
what did you say
Did he give you his contact information?
Yeah
He entered it himself
Why is he so abnormal?
Abominable
So you just went crazy over there?
No more
I decided to face reality
I am no longer a young man who can act recklessly
Like it, like it
To keep the routine I worked so hard to build from falling apart
I made up my mind to give up my life
Son, Kota Kinabalu is so beautiful
Damn Kota Kinabalu
What do you mean I have to give up my thoughts? I hear you farting.
Look how fast your reaction is
Brother, I didn’t do it
I really made up my mind to give up.
Hey, what's going on now?
I forget it
Why are you like this too?
Are you waiting for someone's call?
What nonsense are you talking about?
At first glance, you can tell that he is waiting for a call from his ex who broke up with her.
has an unusual taste
Did he really do this?
Excuse me, don’t you have an extra piece of clothing?
Lots of clothes…
(Breaking Out Outfits)
I didn't
What to do
Do we have clothes for the guests to wear?
We can’t let you wear sportswear either
Shi Lie, you’re here
Can we start filming right away?
Okay, let him touch up his makeup a little and we can start.
This way please
What happened to him
what happened?
Hyun Woo
What's wrong
Come over here
May I ask how many clothes you have?
Sometimes brother lie's clothes
Please lend me some
No, that's sponsored by the manufacturer.
But the clothes are worn, is that okay?
-Of course. -Let's go.
Teacher Aijun, this is for you
OK thank you
You change your clothes first
Wait until the shooting is over
- Just give it back to the agent over there. - Okay.
This is Shi Yeol's clothes
How could I be willing to wear such a precious thing...
It tastes so good too
quiet
Although you all know him, I still want to formally introduce him.
This is the trainee teacher who will be working at our school in the next few weeks.
Teacher Choi Si Yeol
Hello everyone
I am the intern teacher of Chinese Language and Literature Choi Si Yeol
Si Yeol’s face that I always see in videos
familiar face
Where were we last class?
Please tell me about your first love
Hello
Don't ask about your first love in class. It will make the teacher very embarrassed.
ok
Why are you asking that kind of thing? Really?
Can you tell me, teacher?
First love?
Were you 18 at that time?
When I'm most restless, nervous and tired
Some people have been unilaterally encouraging me from the sidelines
It's mine...
A-One Chu
teacher
It's true
I like them the most
Now I love them very much
-We One Chu love you more Shi Lie
-Okay, let's start the class.
-Okay -Okay
You can start teaching from here
good
Okay, Teacher Shilie will read the text. Listen attentively.
-Okay -Okay
In that birch forest blooming with unknown flowers
I recall the past
My grandma who lived in the cabin once said
A breeze, a blade of grass
Even a drop of dew
All have their reasons for existing
Grandma often stops on the trail
And caress the still stone
This stone may be supporting someone's path
Or is it helping the rainwater flow through?
Then we'll go up here
Let’s applaud today’s trainee teachers.
Okay, don’t forget your homework. You must do it.
-Okay -Okay
Teacher, you have to come to our class next time too
Let's go
-Thank you. Shiyeol. You really did a good job.
Ah yes thank you
Teacher, can you take a photo with us?
Sorry, we are very busy. We will shoot next time
-I'm sorry -I'm sorry -What a shame
Hey, you guys go back to study
-Okay -Okay
Different atmosphere…
Did something really happen?
Didn’t you say you wanted to eat school meals?
How is it
So delicious
especially this
this is what i like
Of course I know
My baby eats more
This is what my mother often made for me when I was little...
Sorry, wait a moment
Let's change the memory card and shoot again
Is this okay, brother?
Take off a little more
Here we go again
That unfamiliar face
You eat a little
Okay, we're going to start shooting again.
Shi Yeol, Teacher Aejun, is that okay?
good
good start
Do teachers eat school meals every day?
what
Yes, we will have school meals
Some people will also go out to eat
But
This sausage is really amazing
Today is your first experience. How does it feel?
Actually I'm worried
But thanks to teacher Luo Aijun who taught me gently
fun to experience
But it's not like it's your first time at all. You taught me very well.
Really?
Always feel so strange
The first day of "Go! Trainee Teacher" ended successfully
I have to get off work today
Then we'll see you in the next class
-Goodbye -Goodbye
Card OK
-Okay, thank you for your hard work. -Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work, Shi Lie
Well, good job
is this right
-Teacher Shi Lie -Teacher Shi Lie This is for you
-Teacher Shi Lie, you are so handsome. -Thank you.
-Teacher Aijun, come here.
-Shilie, you are so handsome. -Okay.
I'll let you take a look at the itinerary
So handsome
He is also very tall
-Because the date needs to be adjusted slightly. -Okay.
No matter what, we can't give it to the students...
Oh yes, clothes
Because things keep happening like I'm dreaming
I might get it wrong for a moment
We'll see each other often in the next few weeks
Let’s get acquainted with it more.
After getting the contact information
I was struggling there and even performed a one-man show.
I really want to call him, I really want to hear his voice
It’s really embarrassing Luo Aijun
You don't need to worry at all, right?
Ah yes thank you
Thank you for your hard work
Sure enough
Is it better to stay in fantasy?
(sedative)
-Thank you for your hard work, brother -Yeah
Brother, I’ll have a chat with the producer and then come back.
Ouch, it feels like it's going to take a long time
You get on the bus first
-我知道了 -好
(Luo Aijun)
Hello
I... am Luo Aijun
i know
Please tell me
The clothes I borrowed from you haven't been returned yet
May I ask where you are now?
Give you your clothes
You can return it to me next time you shoot
But still…
Also
this
I saw what you put in your pocket
I'm afraid that pretending not to see it will make you even more unhappy.
good
Then we'll see you next time we shoot
That...
I think it's a bit over the line to say that.
I was still hesitating whether to say it or not.
Because you looked tired during the shoot
That's when you hint to me
what do you mean
Like you don't eat or something like that
Maybe you are like this
But you sometimes look unhappy...
If I think too much
Then I'm sorry
I said the wrong thing
Who are you? Why are you talking so much?
That's right
Because I have neurogastritis
It’s hard to eat during filming
Since the drink attack three years ago
The company decided to throw away all outside food
-So... -But
You said I look glum sometimes
That's not because I'm in bad shape
what
Otherwise...
It’s because of you, Teacher Luo Aijun
what
Please tell me what did I do wrong?
After exchanging contact information, I also sent you a message first.
But you didn't reply
Are you trying to draw a clear line with me?
Me?
Please give me some advice for today’s shooting.
How dare I...
Don’t reply to the messages sent by your life.
I didn't mean it
It seems that I didn’t notice it when I was busy working.
It’s true. How could I not reply to your message?
So things are not as expected
Makes me feel bored and lost
So I didn’t look at your face all day today
But how can someone like you feel disappointed with me?
I'm very...how should I put it?
Can't quite understand
I've made it so clear
You still don’t understand?
You don't seem to hate me
I'm flirting now
Flirting with Teacher Luo Aijun
From the first time we met until now, I have always loved you...
Very interested
"My idol is chasing me?!"
Kuisheng said he wanted to break up with me
I don't know what to do
You can't treat Brother Zhu He like this
We can't treat Brother Zhu He like that
He said he did have a new partner
Do you want to meet today?
I am very interested in Teacher Luo
Please…
Do you have a date?